A Team Nanban (594mgnav) Release
（ｱﾃﾅ）
西暦2133年 非核大戦によって
平和と秩序は崩壊した
In the year 2133...
the world was thrust
into an era of devastation and Chaos.
人類はその半数が死滅
More than half of the Earth's population
was killed off by nonnuclear global war.
大戦によって負傷した多くの人々は
サイボーグとして再生した
It was only a matter of time
before the planet itself...
2135年 停戦と共に中立都市
オリュンポスが生まれ
would become utterly uninhabitable
and all life there would cease to exist.
世界で起こる
紛争の調停にあたった
Humans searched
for a last Seed of hope.
When they could not find it,
they created one:
世界の調和にして秩序
オリュンポスには人とサイボーグ
Olympus.
In this utopia, those injured in the war
were reconditioned as human cyborgs.
そして 人の遺伝子で作られ
怒りや憎しみを抑制された種族―
International disputes were buffered
by a breed of genetically engineered...
バイオロイドが共存していた
humans cal/ed bioroids, who were
designed never to feel anger or hatred.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
犯人の武装集団は
会議に向かうＥＵ高官を人質に
All right, gang, listen up.
We got a heavily armed group
holed up in an abandoned Church...
廃棄された聖堂に
立てこもっている
with top-ranking EU officials
as hostages.
ヤツらの動機 要求 人数
構成などは全て不明
Don't know who they are
or what they want.
地元警察も
手が出せない状況だ
Local police haven't taken them down,
so you know the drill.
敵は戦闘サイボーグを
含む可能性がある
You could be looking at Combat cyborgs.
注意しろ
突入は22:45ジャストだ
We move in at 2245 sharp.
22:30で時刻合わせ
Synchronize your watches
to 2230 on my mark.
３ ２ １ ナウ
Three, two, one...
now.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
ふんっ 最新のサイボーグに
アナログ時計か
A high-tech cyborg wearing
an analog watch. Well, look at that.
似合わねえな
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
こいつは俺と同じで
鼓動を刻んでるのさ
Has its own heartbeat, just like I do.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
音を狙い撃ちされるぞ
The sound of it will get your ass shot.
言ってやれよ デュナン
パートナーだろ
Tell him, Deunan. He's your partner.
ヘヘヘッ まったく
いいコンビだよ
Well, I'll be.
You two are made for each other.
（隊員１）
目標接近 降下地点確認
Approaching landing zone.
Drop point confirmed.
（隊員２）
降下地点クリア　全部隊 降下しろ
Drop point clear. All units, deploy.
（隊員３）
急げ！　時間がないぞ！
Let's go! We don't have much time!
I'm outside the corridor and I'm going in.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
外部回路に着いた
これから侵入する
（隊員）
突入30秒前 準備よし！
Launch assault in 30 seconds.
All units, stand by.
（ｻｲﾎﾞｰｸﾞ）
おら！
（隊員）
聖堂内部に せん光弾確認
- Flash grenade inside the Cathedral.
- Damn you, Deunan.
デュナンめ　直ちに突入しろ！
All right, prepare to move in.
On my count.
カウント３　３ ２ １
Three, two, one.
Kill them!
（ｻｲﾎﾞｰｸﾞ）
撃て 撃て！
（隊員１）右クリア
（隊員２）上にもいます
Cover me. Fire!
Secure the hostages.
（隊員３）
人質を確保しろ！
大丈夫か？
You all right?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）人質を頼む
（隊員）はい
- Watch the hostage.
- Got it.
（ｻｲﾎﾞｰｸﾞたち）
えい！
They're all cyborgs.
What the hell's going on?
全員サイボーグって
どういうこと？
Let's ask them.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
聞いてみるしかないな
I think they're in the mood to talk now.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
おとなしくなったみたいだな
お前らの目的はなんだ？
聞こえるか？　答えろ！
Who are you? What do you want?
Do you hear me? Answer me.
全ては… １つに…
我はハルコン…
All will be one. We will all be one.
I am Halcon.
He's gonna blow. Move it.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
マズい 自爆か！
Deunan, are you all right?
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
大丈夫か？　デュナン
Briareos?
ブリアレオス
Briareos! Don't...
ブリアレオス！
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
待て デュナン！
- Deunan, stop.
- Let go.
離せ！　離せよ アイアコス！
Let go of me, goddamn it!
ブリアレオス！　ブリアレオス～！
Briareos. Briareos!
Attention, all units. We have a
disturbance reported in Sector B-47...
（隊員）
Ｂ47地区で
工事用ランドメイトが暴れている
invo/ving a construction Landmate.
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.に出動要請
Request ES. Vl/.A. T. Dispatch.
第２班は直ちにデルタ編成で―
Team 2, proceed to WASP hangar
in Delta Formation at once.
マスク格納庫へ　繰り返す
Repeat, disturbance in Sector B-47.
Request ES. Vl/.A. T. Dispatch.
Ｂ47地区で
工事用ランドメイトが暴れている
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.に出動要請
Team 2, report to the WASP hangar
in Delta Formation at once.
第２班は直ちにデルタ編成で…
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ランス隊長
Captain.
- Deunan?
- I heard the call.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
デュナンか？
今の聞いたわ
Ｂ47ならすぐの所にいるんだけど
I'm near B-47 right now.
Aren't you supposed to be
off-duty today?
お前 今日非番だろ？
Well, things change.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
もう 現場に着いたみたい
We're on our way.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
こっちもすぐに合流する
ムチャするなよ デュナン！
Don't do anything stupid, Deunan.
You hear me?
（作業員１）
来るな！　来るな！
Run! Run!
随分にぎやかじゃない？
- What's happening?
- He got fired.
（作業員２）
あの野郎 クビになった腹いせに
ランドメイトで暴れだしやがった！
Next thing you know,
he grabbed a Landmate.
He's going to turn the place...
Oh, God.
Get up.
立て！
- Where's the kill switch?
- On his back.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
停止スイッチは？
（作業員）
背中の上に！　うわっ…
Unit 1 ready.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
発進します
どいつもこいつも
バカにしやがって！　おら！
Don't treat me like a fool!
おりゃ！
Goddamn you!
You're late.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
遅い
Got it. I saw it.
チャンス？　分かってるわよ
（ﾗﾝﾄﾞﾒｲﾄ）
てめえ！　うお～！
Damn it!
うわ！　クソッ
Get off of me! Damn it!
やめろ！　てめえ！
降りろ！　チクショー
Get off! Shit! Get off!
ク… クソ！
You little bitch! Get off!
（ﾗﾝﾄﾞﾒｲﾄ）
この野郎　くっ！　動かねえぞ
What are you doing?
Let me out of here.
You bitch!
出る幕なしか　やりすぎだぞ！
Looks like we missed the party.
I told you to play it cool.
Where is he?
犯人は？
Back there, on the ground.
あそこで固まってます
新入り？
Who's the new guy?
Oh, yeah, right.
そうだったな　紹介しておこう
I have to introduce you.
Some other time, Lance.
Today is my day off.
あしたでいいです
本部でまた
Deunan Knute, meet Tereus.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
彼の名はテレウス
お前の新しいパートナーだ
Your new partner.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
どういうことですか？　ニケ参長
What the hell are you thinking, Nike?
Watch your mouth, Deunan.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
口を慎め デュナン
Did you forget that my
partner is in the hospital?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオスは今も
危険な状態が続いてるんです
こんな時になぜ？
- I can't believe that you'd do this to me.
- Well, believe it.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
言ったはずだ
Tereus is the only one whose
fighting potential compares to Briareos.
テレウスはブリアレオスの
欠員を補う重要な戦力だ
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
そんなこと
聞いてるんじゃありません！
That's not what I'm talking about
and you know it.
Why does your new partner
look remarkably similar to Briareos...
（ニケ）
なぜ サイボーグになる前の
ブリアレオスと―
同じ顔のバイオロイドを
配属したのか？
before he became a cyborg?
Isn't that what you want to know?
そう聞きたいのだな？
ついてきなさい デュナン
Come with me, Deunan.
This facility is, for the most part,
just like its predecessor.
知ってのとおり
我々バイオロイドは―
人の遺伝子を元に
目的に合わせてデザインされ
We continue to create bioroids
from the very same DNA as you humans...
genetically deleting negative emotions.
作られた存在だ
As you know, bioroids are, more often
than not, diplomats, emissaries...
人と違ってバイオロイドは
感情が抑制されている
オリュンポスの犯罪が
圧倒的に少ないのも
and, like your friend Hitomi,
ministers of political affairs.
我々が人社会の緩衝材に
なっているからだ
Bioroids must act as a
regulating force within society.
だが 世界では
いまだ争いの火が絶えない
So we decided to produce bioroids
with high Combat capabilities...
治安維持のためにも
to further uphold public order.
戦闘能力の高い
バイオロイドを生産することにした
テレウスは そのテストケースだ
Tereus is serving as our prototype.
彼は法と秩序を守るために戦う
He fights to preserve law and order.
人のように怒りや
憎しみを原動力に戦いはしない
And unlike humans, anger and hatred
will never influence his decision to fight.
彼の遺伝子情報は―
The majority of his genetic code
was taken from Briareos.
そのほとんどが
ブリアレオスのものだ
なぜ ブリアレオスなんですか？
Why did you choose Briareos?
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.隊員の
戦闘データを比較した結果
After analyzing Combat data
from all soldiers in ES.W.A.T...
we found him to be by far
the most qualified of all candidates.
彼が我々の望む条件を
最も満たしていた
それに彼は―
And then there is
his Hecatonchire-class body.
あのヘカトンケイル級の
マシンボディーに適合できた
Briareos is the only person who
has been able to adapt to it.
ただ一人の人間だ
その強じんな体力と精神力は
注目に値する
His physical and mental strength
is truly remarkable.
だからこそ ブリアレオスの
パートナーだったきみに
You were his former partner.
That's why we need you to
assess Tereus' capabilities.
テレウスの能力を
見極めてほしいのだ
I won't do it.
納得できません！
I'm not asking.
これは決定事項だ！
（ﾋﾄﾐ）デュナン
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）ヒトミ
- Deunan.
- Hitomi, you're back.
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
海外視察から今戻ったの
I just got back from
the World Trade Expo.
聞いたわ ブリアレオスのこと
I heard about Briareos.
はい
- Yes?
- Deunan, it's Lance.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
デュナン
ブリアレオスの意識が戻ったぞ
Briareos is waking up.
えっ ホントですか！
I'll be right there.
（ｱﾃﾅ）
我がオリュンポス政府が
提唱する―
As the prime minister of Olympus...
I strong/y advocate
a global security network.
（ｱﾃﾅ）
グローバル･
セキュリティー･ネットは
世界各国の観測 通信衛星を
オリュンポスが統合管理することで
This would entail bringing
all the world's surveillance...
as well as communication satellites
under the control of Olympus.
同時多発テロへの
監視力を強化する…
This will enhance our....
ねえ あれ何？
Hey, what...? What are those things?
フッ 相変わらず
はやりに疎いな デュナンは
Always behind the times,
aren't you, Deunan?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
もったいぶらない
Yeah, yeah.
ほら これ
Here, check it out.
It's called a Connexus.
コネクサスって言ってね
It's the most advanced personal
multimedia terminal ever made.
脳波から直接ネットワークに
アクセスできる―
マルチメディア端末のこと
着けてみて
Makes life so much easier.
Try it on.
次世代携帯端末ってところかな
Everybody's got one.
It's an amazing piece of technology.
オリジナルの制作者は不明だけど
And anyone can use it just by accessing
the free open-source Codes.
ネット上のオープンソースで
誰にでもコピーが作れるの
今じゃ 世界のヒット商品よ
That's the best thing about it.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ふ～ん
あっ 右のメッセージ開いてみて
Hey, go ahead
and open that message on the right.
何？
What is it?
A birthday party?
誕生パーティー？
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
フフッ 絶対来てね
Promise me you'll come, okay?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ヒトミって いくつになったの？
So how old are you gonna be?
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
秘密
Just because I'm a bioroid doesn't
mean that I'll tell you my age.
バイオロイドに年
聞くもんじゃないわ
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス
Briareos.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
おっと 待った！
抱きつくのはなしだぜ
Hold it right there, honey.
You have to be gentle, all right?
せっかく つながったボディーが
また バラバラになっちまう
After all, they just put him back together.
ほれ
We should be able to be release him
in just over a week.
（ｹｽﾅｰ）
この状態なら１週間程で退院だよ
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ホントですか？　先生
- Are you serious?
- He's a lucky man.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
ブリアレオスは幸運だよ
ドクター ケスナーは
Dr. Kestner is the Chief
professor at the academy...
オリュンポス科学アカデミーの
筆頭教授で
サイボーグ医療のエキスパートだ
間違いない
not to mention the foremost expert
on cyborg medical science.
それに 俺の主治医でもある
Your buddy's in good hands.
Hell, he's even my doctor.
ハハハッ 褒めすぎだよ
You're being too kind, I'm afraid.
じゃ 私はこれで
I'll leave you all to your visit.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
で 事件のほうは？
So, what's new?
It's like we thought it was.
現場検証の結果
The investigation at the Church
revealed all the terrorists were cyborgs.
やっぱりテログループは
全員がサイボーグだったらしいわ
We've taken another look
at the five most recent terror incidents.
最近発生した５件のテロ事件を
再調査した結果
うち４件が
サイボーグによる犯行だった
Four were carried out entirely by cyborgs.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
サイボーグによるテロ…
目的はなんです？
Cyborg terrorists? What are they after?
That's what I'd like to know.
But we do have a couple of leads to go on.
まだ不明だ
しかし 手がかりはある
現場付近で異常電波が確認された
We've found unidentified frequencies,
all of them in the surrounding areas.
戦時中に開発された
洗脳用のウイルスプログラムと
よく似てるらしい
Pattern looks like
a puppet-master program from the war.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
犯人たちが操られていたと？
They're being brainwashed.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
その可能性もあるってことだ
It's a possibility.
俺たちと違ってプロテクトの
甘いパーツを使っている―
The problem is that most
cyborgs out there...
have poorly protected
systems, unlike us.
サイボーグはごまんといる
そいつらを利用して
テロをたくらんでるとしたら…
If someone is manipulating
civilian cyborgs for terrorist acts...
Things are gonna get a lot hotter
on our end.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
頭の痛い話だ
Furthermore, we have no idea
who we're dealing with or what they want.
しかし 敵の目的も
組織も見当がつかん
- So get off your ass, we need you.
- What are you talking about?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
寝てる場合じゃないよ ブリ
ムチャ言うな
こんな状態で動けるか！
I can't go on active duty like this.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ねえ いつ取れるの？
このコードの束
When can all these wires come off?
バカ！　おい引っ張るなって！
おいやめろよ！
- Don't pull. You're not my doctor.
- Come on.
Let go of that.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
おい デュナン
それぐらいにしといてやれよ
Here we go again.
（隊員）
また始まったな
Here, I fixed it for you.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
これ 修理しておいた
This thing's tougher than I am.
俺より丈夫だな
You heard about the new guy,
Tereus, right?
聞いた？
テレウスってヤツのこと
Yeah. Before you came.
お前が来る前にな
どんなヤツが来ても
私にとってブリは１人だよ
Well, I don't care what they say.
You're my partner,
no matter what happens.
Deunan, get back!
戻れ デュナン！
- Deunan, talk to me. Are you all right?
- Briareos.
デュナン 大丈夫か？
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス？
私 生きてるよね？
Am I...?
Am I alive?
ああ　生きてる
Yeah, you're alive.
ありがとう
Thank you.
I'll always protect you,
even if the world comes to an end.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
たとえ世界が終わっても
お前を守ってみせるよ
I know you will.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス
ポセイドン特使 吉野(よしの)です
I am Yoshino from Poseidon.
オリュンポス政策参事長ニケです
アテナ行政総監がお待ちです
And I am Nike,
the Chief of staff of Olympus.
Prime Minister Athena
has been expecting you.
As you can see, many of the cyborgs
involved in the terrorist incidents...
（ｱﾃﾅ）
テロを引き起こした
サイボーグたちはご覧のとおり
ほとんどが
ポセイドンのパーツを使っている
were equipped with Components
made by Poseidon.
I would like to know...
この件に関して
吉野特使の見解は？
what are your thoughts on the matter,
Emissary Yoshino?
We have tracked down
the cyborg parts in question...
（吉野）
問題のサイボーグ部品を
出荷したラボを
シリアルナンバーから割り出し
即刻 閉鎖しました
to the lab that manufactured them,
and shut it down immediately.
Other departments have enacted
countermeasures as well.
それ以外の部署でも
万全の対策をとっています
However...
しかし―
it would be regrettable
to draw connections...
テロとポセイドンをそれ以上
関連づけられるのは心外です
between these terrorists and Poseidon.
So then you're saying Poseidon had nothing
to do with the latest terrorist attacks?
では ポセイドンと今回のテロには
なんの関係もないと？
Prime minister, you're well aware...
ご存じのようにポセイドンは
世界最大の企業集合体です
that Poseidon is the largest
industrial conglomerate in the world.
その収益のほとんどが
諸外国との貿易で成り立っています
Our profits come from trade
with other countries.
Siding with terrorists would give
no financial benefits whatsoever.
テロなどに加担しても
なんの利益も生みません
オリュンポスが我が社の製品を
ボイコットすれば
If Olympus were to boycott our products,
other countries would follow your lead.
他国も右へならうでしょう
企業としては大きな損失です
Clearly, the negative impact
would not be in our best interest.
事件に関与した
可能性のある会社には―
That may be, but we have issued
the same message...
全て同様の通達をした
to all the businesses
that may have been involved.
ポセイドンだけを
特別扱いはできない
We cannot afford to give Poseidon
special consideration.
今度の国際会議の議題は
One of the topics at
the peace conference...
オリュンポスによる衛星の
総合管理と監視システムの強化
is your desire to
enhance surveillance...
by controlling
international satellite systems...
is it not?
でしたね？
ポセイドンの持つ
衛星ネットをコントロールする―
This hyper-sheath contains the master
control program to our satellite network.
コードプログラムです
どうぞ お使いください
Consider it a gift.
- Cutting a deal, are we?
- Our contribution to global welfare.
取り引きか？
これは国際貢献です
Not something I'd expect to hear
from a business that makes tools for war.
戦争の道具を売っている
企業の言葉とは思えないな
ならば お聞きします
Olympus is no stranger
to military prowess.
オリュンポスの軍事力は
なんのために？
力無くして世界が守れるとでも？
You know that you can't
protect the world without force.
この件は
もう一度 協議してみよう
We'll review our options and
speak with you at another time.
よいお返事を
お待ちしております
We will look forward
to a favorable reply.
おっ ありがとう
Great. Keep them coming.
（男性１）おめでとう
（女性）誕生日おめでとう ヒトミ
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, Hitomi.
（男性２）
ハッピーバースデー
Happy birthday.
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
皆さん 今夜は集まってくれて
ホントにありがとう！
It was so sweet of you all
to come tonight.
ゆっくり
楽しんでいってくださいね
I hope all of you have a great time.
（義経(よしつね)）
おめでとう ヒトミ
You look great. Happy birthday.
Thank you, Yoshitsune.
ありがとう 義経君
Looks like you've got a
surprise guest hiding over there.
誰だ？
そこでコソコソしてるのは？
ほら！　いいかげん
こっちに来て！
Come on, get over here. Come on.
- Well, take a look at Deunan.
- You clean up nice.
（男性）誰かと思ったよ
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）驚いたな
へえ～
Well...
あ… いや… もういいよ
- Yeah.
- Okay, enough already.
ウフフッ
（女性）おめでとう ヒトミ
（ﾋﾄﾐ）ありがとう
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday.
おめでとう ヒトミ　じゃ！
Have a good time.
今日は あなたにも
いいことがあるのよ
We have good things in store
for you tonight too.
- Just look over there.
- What?
ほら あそこ！
ブリアレオス 治ったんだね？
Briareos.
- Does this mean you're okay?
- Not quite.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
いや カメラアイがまだおかしい
Something's wrong with my eyescope.
見たこともないデュナンが見える
I'm seeing a Deunan that
I've never seen before.
あっ… いや…
Tonight we're also celebrating
Briareos' full recovery.
今日はブリアレオスの
全快祝いも兼ねてるのよ
そうだったの
I had no idea.
Happy birthday, Hitomi.
ヒトミ政務次官おめでとう
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
ああ～ キレイ！
ありがとうございます
How lovely.
Thank you so much.
Oh, yeah. You two still haven't met yet,
have you?
そうか お前は初めてだったな
Briareos, meet Tereus.
彼がテレウスだ
ようやく会えました
はじめまして
Well, Briareos at last.
It's nice to meet you.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
今日は仮装パーティーか？
Is this supposed to be a Costume party?
This guy's wearing a mask
with my old face.
昔の俺の顔を
かぶったヤツがいるぜ
好きで かぶっているわけじゃない
To be honest,
it wasn't exactly my own choice.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ハッ ハハハッ
そういう言い方までそっくりとはな
Sounds exactly like me too.
フンッ
これでコンビ復活ですね
So I have my old partner back now?
I meant to talk to you about that.
そのことだがな デュナン
お前にはもう少し
テレウスと組んでもらう
Afraid I need you to Stick with Tereus
a little longer.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
俺は当分
アイアコスと組むことにした
- I'll team up with Aeacus for a while.
- What do you mean?
どういう意味？
I saw your Combat data with him.
Not bad.
お前たちの戦闘データを見た
悪くない
本気で言ってるの？
私はイヤだよ！
Wait, is this some kind of joke?
Because I'm not laughing.
俺がホントにぶっ壊れちまった時
お前は誰と組むつもりだ？
Think about it, Deunan.
They fixed me twice.
Who are you gonna partner with...
- ...if they can't do it a third time?
- Then I won't partner with anyone.
誰とも組まないよ！
（義経）ああ～
（ﾋﾄﾐ）デュナン
Deunan.
Seems Briareos was pretty worried
about you.
ブリアレオスが心配してたよ
Do I look like I care?
よく言うよ！
勝手にいろいろ決めといて
And so what if he is, anyway?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）もう１本
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）コーヒーにして
- Another one.
- Better make that a coffee.
エスプレッソ
リキュール落として
Espresso. With a shot of liqueur.
気に入られてないのは
分かってるけど
Look, Deunan,
I know you're not too fond of me...
俺は君がパートナーで
よかったと思ってる
but I gotta admit that I'm really glad
they Chose you as my partner.
All I ask is that you Stick with me
a little longer.
もう少し
俺と つきあってくれ
どうかした？
What's the matter?
Did Briareos tell you
how I like to drink it?
ブリアレオスから聞いたの？
私の好きな飲み方
いや
No.
帰って
Go home.
I'll drop you off.
送るよ
Leave me alone.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
１人にして
あなたといると
頭がゴチャゴチャしてくる
I get Confused.
I get Confused when I'm with you.
はあ～ 分かった
No problem.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
ヘカトンケイルっていうのは
The Hecatonchires were giants
with a hundred arms, right?
100本腕の巨人って
意味なんだってな
ギリシャ神話に出てくる言葉だ
That's mythology...
but now it's a system that can control
multiple external networks.
無数の外部端末を
集中制御できるシステムだ
And you are the only one,
the only man they could find...
お前はただ１人
ヘカトンケイル級の
マシンボディーに―
who was able to adapt
to the H-class machine body.
適応できた人間ってわけだ
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
それだけ
リスクを背負ってるってことさ
Yeah, yeah. Lucky me.
It sure sucks, don't it,
being a cyborg and all?
う～ん 因果だな
お互いサイボーグっていうのは
It has its drawbacks.
まったくだ
So, what you gonna do, pretty boy?
で どうすんだ 色男？
With Deunan, I mean.
デュナンのことだよ
Not too many girls out there
who'll stay with you...
マシンボディーになっても
付いてきてくれる子なんぞ
なかなかいないぞ！
once you're more of a machine
than a man.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ああ 分かってるさ
だから難しいんだ
It hasn't crossed my mind.
屈折してるんだよ！
お前の愛は
Nobody ever said love was easy, pal.
What about you? You got a girl?
お前こそ女でも？
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ほら そのピアス
She making you wearjewelry?
Oh, you mean this.
これか
コネクサスって言うんだと
No, it's just my Connexus.
娘がな
おそろいなんだとよ
My daughter gave it to me.
She's got one to match it.
サイボーグになっても
家族の愛があるってわけか
What, you're being a cyborg
isn't enough metal on you already?
Once you start you can't stop.
やくなよ！
誰が！
- You're an addict.
- Hey, don't break the merchandise.
痛いって
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
アリアンス国際会議場の前に―
Leaders from all over the world are arriving
now amid both fanfare and heavy security.
各国首脳を乗せた車が
次々と到着しています
All cyborgs have been cleared
from the premises, sir.
（隊員）
エリア内のサイボーグは完全退去
引き続き検問を続けます
Continuing security checks.
デュナン 始まるぞ
Deunan, time to go.
- Right.
- What's wrong?
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
どうした？
About the other night, I...
この間は… ごめん
- Sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
気にするな
俺は君のパートナーだ
We're partners.
I've got your back, no matter what.
何があってもバックアップするよ
I guess I can count on you.
頼もしいじゃん
You didn't know that?
知らなかったのか？
This worldwide peace summit
and conference of dignitaries...
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
厳戒態勢の中 今 世界の未来を担う
会議が始まろうとしています
may very well forge our future.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will now open discussions to the floor.
ただ今より
安全保障会議を開催いたします
Prime Minister Athena is in.
We are green.
（隊員）
アテナ総監入りました
始まったようです
Okay.
よし 各部署 気を抜くなよ！
All units, look alive. Here we go.
Looks like it's starting.
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
始まったらしいぜ
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ああ 何もないといいが
All right. Let's hope nothing happens.
何かあっても
俺たちがいるから大丈夫さ
Don't sweat it, partner.
If the shit hits the fan,
ES.W.A.T. will handle it.
Hell, that's why they pay us the big bucks,
isn't it?
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.は
最高のチームだぜ！
（ニケ）
各国の情報衛星を
統合することにより
And by merging
each country's satellite systems...
we will create a unified
global communications network.
戦争で混乱した
情報ネットワークを再構築し
紛争やテロを
未然に抑えることができるのです
Ladies and gentlemen,
we believe this will quell conflicts...
情報の共有こそが
今の我々に求められているのです
and terrorist attacks
before they ever happen...
helping ensure peace
for future generations.
Obviously, this was simply an overview
of the proposed global security network.
以上がオリュンポスが提案する―
グローバル･セキュリティー･
ネットの概要です
For the good of mankind, I urge you all...
各国の衛星を―
一時的にオリュンポスの
管理下に置くことを
to place your countries' satellites
under Olympus' control.
ご承認いただきたい
（首脳１）
先日の我が国のテロは―
The recent incident
that occurred in our country...
オリュンポスの
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.によって
was handled by the Olympus ES.W.A.T.
In a very expeditious manner.
迅速に解決されました
そういう協力関係のネットワークの
ためにも この提案の…
A truly secure network, as you propose,
would be a phenomenal...
（首脳２）
いいや！　我が国は
オリュンポスに頼らなくとも
My country already has the means
to protect itself from terrorism...
without having to rely on
Olympus' support.
テロから身を守るすべくらいはある
Or perhaps your country might have things
you don't want anyone else to see.
（首脳３）
見られてはマズいものでも
あるように聞こえますな
何か言いたいことでも
あるようですな
What do you mean?
Would you care to elaborate on that?
我々は貴国が
いくつかの紛争をバックアップ…
Sources indicate that your country
supports several regional conflicts...
That's ridiculous!
How dare you make such an accusation.
（首脳２）
バカバカしい！　言いがかりだ！
大体 なぜ我々 人が
バイオロイドの統治する―
Enough of this. Why should Olympus
be in control of the satellite systems?
オリュンポスの
管轄下に置かれるのか！
- How do we know bioroids can be trusted?
- I agree.
（首脳４）
よしたまえ！
This discussion
has nothing to do with race.
（首脳２）
こんな会議などムダだ！
（警告音）
（隊員）異常電波を確認しました
Captain, I'm detecting
an unidentified data frequency.
微弱ですが
（ﾗﾝｽ）
異常電波だと？
- From where?
- Multiple signals. They're everywhere.
（隊員）
発信源は… 拡散しています！
All units, be on the alert.
各班 警戒態勢！
ランドメイト部隊も発信準備！
Landmate units, prepare to move out.
Code 3.
コンディション３
All right, Aeacus. Let's move.
アイアコス 出るぞ
You go on ahead.
Just give me a minute, buddy.
すまんが 先に行っててくれ
I'll be right behind you.
俺もすぐ出る
大丈夫か？
You all right?
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
なんでもない
- I'll be okay.
- Okay.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ１）
よし 行け
All right, you can go.
Next.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ２）
次！
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ３）
止まれ！
Hey.
（ポリス２）おい！
（ポリス１）ん？
Stop.
止まれ！　止まるんだ！
うわ～！
Stop. I said stop!
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ４）
止まれ
- It's not stopping.
- We're gonna have to take him out.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ５）
ダメです 突っ込んできます！
かまわん！　撃て！
Fire. Fire.
Disturbance reported at Gate E-12.
（隊員１）
Ｅ12ゲートで爆発確認
（隊員２）
Ｅ12ゲート要員 報告せよ
Okay, Aeacus. I'm heading out.
アイアコス 先に出るぞ
（隊員１）
こちらタルタロス 正面Ａ２ゲート
暴走車が次々と突入してきます！
This is Tartaros, Front Gate, A-2.
Unauthorized vehicles
have breached the outer perimeter.
This is Gate F-7.
Our position is also being overrun.
（隊員２）
同じくＦゲート こちらも同様です
Copy that.
Keep the premises Secure at all cost.
とにかく暴走車を１台も入れるな
ランドメイトをもっと投入しろ
Order the Landmates
to start mobilizing now.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
デュナンとテレウスは
そのエリアのポリスを援護しろ
Deunan, Tereus, I need you to
back up the police in the area.
会場にテロリストを近づけるな
Keep the assailants away
from the conference hall.
Yes, sir.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
了解
Minister, areas around the conference hall
are under attack.
会議場周辺で暴走車による
襲撃が起きています
いったん ここは中断して
避難を
Suspend proceedings
and ensure your safety.
Nonsense. We will continue.
無用だ　このまま続ける
Unauthorized Landmate. Fire.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
ランドメイトだ 撃て！
It's a construction Landmate.
工事用ランドメイトまで？
It's not a cyborg.
サイボーグじゃない
これは ただの人だ…
What's going on here?
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
大丈夫か デュナン？
Deunan. You okay?
Yeah.
うっ うう… なんだこいつら？
What the hell is going on here?
Those aren't cyborgs. They're humans.
サイボーグだけじゃない
人もこの暴動に加わっています
（隊員）
急いでください
You still here?
４か所以上で
暴動が起きているようです
Better get down there,
sounds like all hell's breaking loose.
（撃鉄を起こす音）
（隊員）アイアコス？
Do you need something?
全ては… １つに…
我はハルコン！
All will be one. We will all be one.
I am Halcon.
Aeacus?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
アイアコス？
（首脳１）
なんだ？　爆発したぞ
- What was that?
- Is it a terrorist?
- We must get out of here.
- It's an explosion. Look!
（首脳２）
テロじゃないのか？
- We stop this meeting immediately.
- We should evacuate.
会議は中止だ！
（首脳３）警備はどうなってるんだ
（首脳４）非難させてくれ 危険だ
Quiet, please.
（ｱﾃﾅ）
お静かに！
There is no need to panic.
This conference hall is heavily fortified.
ご心配なく　議場の安全は
このアテナが保証いたします
Gentlemen, please return to your seats.
皆さん 席にお戻りください
Let us resume the discussion.
会議を続けましょう
Aeacus. What's wrong? Answer me.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
アイアコス どうした？
答えろ アイアコス！
（銃声）
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）やめろ！
Stop it!
- Everyone get back!
- Get out!
（首脳１）倒れるぞ！
（首脳２）危ない！
（首脳３）
こんな状況で会議などできるか！
Let's get out of here.
Take a good look!
ご覧なさい
これが今の世界の現実です
This is the reality of the world
we now live in.
皆さんの決断が
求められているのです
The time to decide on
this proposal is now.
Or do you want to create
more unnecessary casualties?
これ以上の犠牲者を
出すつもりなのですか？
Stop! Aeacus!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
やめるんだ アイアコス！
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
ブリアレオス！
Briareos!
All will be one. Do you understand?
全ては１つ… 分かるか？
Stop it!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
やめろ！
しまった
Damn it!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
やめろ！
やめるんだ アイアコス！
Stop it. Aeacus!
（ｱｲｱｺｽ）
おりゃ～！
Aeacus, no!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
アイアコ～ス！
Aeacus, why?
アイアコス なぜ？
Briareos.
ブリア… レオス…
Briareos, I...
俺は… あっ うおっ…
ブリアレオス
Briareos!
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
こいつはロボットだ
It's a robot!
The frequency's coming from the doves.
不信電波の発信源はハトか？
Looks like the Tartaros Conference Hall
is stabilized and under control.
（隊員）
会議場周辺のテロリストは
制圧した模様
うん？　消えた？
Signal's gone.
（男たちのうめき声）
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）おい！
Hey. What's happening to them?
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
どうしたんだ？　急に
The attackers at each of the gates
have been suppressed.
（隊員１）
各ゲートの暴動 鎮圧しました
負傷者多数
Several casualties.
（隊員２）
異常電波も全て消滅
The unidentified data frequency
seems to have vanished.
（隊員３）
会議も再開しました
The Lord has called
our brother Aeacus home.
（男性）
主は私たちの兄弟 アイアコスを
ご自分の元へお召しになったのです
彼のために祈りましょう
Let us pray for his soul.
Earth to earth, ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
土は土に 灰は灰に 塵(ちり)は塵に
主はアイアコスを高みに導かれ
永遠の安息を与えられます
May the Lord lead him unto heaven
and grant him...
eternal rest.
Am I stable?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
俺は正気だと思うか？
あの時 ドロドロに溶けた
アイアコスの顔が―
I saw his face melt away...
as he attacked me.
俺に迫ってくる気がした
俺もすでに
おかしくなっているのかもしれない
What if I'm losing my sanity too?
You worry too much.
考えすぎだ
Everyone knows
that you did what you had to do.
みんながあんたの
正当性を認めている
Salute.
敬礼！
What are you looking for?
（ｹｽﾅｰ）
何が気になる？
Your flesh has melded with the matrix
of the Hecatonchire system so perfectly...
ヘカトンケイルシステムと
君の肉体のバランスは―
you're practically a work of art.
芸術的とも言えるレベルにある
Have faith. If this technology doesn't
work, no cyborg is safe from this Chaos.
それが信用できないのなら
安全なサイボーグなどありえないよ
I know what happened to Aeacus
came as a terrible shock...
アイアコス君のことは
ショックだろうが
but something like that
could never happen to you.
君にはあんなことは
起こりえない
I see.
そうですか
ありがとうございました
Thanks, doc.
Briareos.
ブリアレオス君
Do you like this city?
君はこの街が好きか？
Do you believe Olympus truly is a utopia
that's worthy of risking your life?
オリュンポスは守るに値する
理想郷か？
I don't know.
分かりません　ただ…
But what I do know is that as long as there's
someone in this city I care about...
そこに大切なものがあれば
俺は守ります
I intend to protect it.
Sacrifice and love, huh?
犠牲と愛か… うん
In all my years, I have found those ideals
led only to human anguish.
人はいつも
そのために苦しみもがく
Wouldn't you agree?
そうは思わんか？
No, I don't.
思いませんね
Not always.
失礼します
Oh, but it does.
いい答えだ
Although the peace conference...
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
オリュンポスの安全保障会議は
テロに襲われながらも
was temporarily disrupted
by an organized attack...
懸案の衛星統合に向け
成功裏に終わりました
discussions ended successfully
with regard to its primary topic...
allowing world leaders to....
これは アテナ総監の
強い指導力を示し…
（ｱﾃﾅ）
オリュンポス議会での討議の結果
As a result of our debate
at the Olympus Assembly...
ポセイドンとの交易は
一部サイボーグパーツを除いて
we will resume normal trade
with Poseidon...
with one notable exception.
Certain cyborg parts.
通常どおり再開する
Thank you, prime minister,
for your consideration.
ご配慮 感謝いたします
早速 本社に報告いたします
I'll let our headquarters know
immediately.
We've received the latest report
on the attack at Tartaros Conference Hall.
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
国際会議場襲撃事件の
調査報告が入りました
- There's something that concerns me.
- What is it?
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）１つ気になることが
（吉野）なんですか？
According to this, one of the rioters
was reported to have said, "I am Halcon."
暴動を起こした人間が
こうつぶやいたそうです
“我はハルコン”
Impossible.
まさか…
ハルコンなど過去の亡霊です
Halcon is nothing more
than a memory.
There's no way they could be involved.
彼らに何ができるというのか
ID Verified.
（隊員）
ＩＤ確認
Thank you.
ご苦労さま
Can I ask you to spar with me?
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
相手してもらえませんか？
Why not ask Deunan?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
デュナンに頼めばいいだろう
I'd prefer to spar with you.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
あなたとやりたいんですよ
えいっ フッ フッ…
えいっ ハッ！
（隊員）
おお やるね
Not bad there, kid.
いいキックだ
That was a good kick.
Are you content now?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
これで満足か？
Nobody can compete with Briareos.
（隊員１）
やっぱブリアレオスには
かなわないか
（隊員２）
いや バイオロイドも
かなりのもんだぜ
That bioroid did fairly well.
We've determined the unidentified data
frequency detected during the incident...
（義経）
先日の事件で 例の異常電波は―
このハトのロボットから
発信されたことが判明しました
was being transmitted
by the robotic doves.
We believe they were responsible.
多分これによって
サイボーグに
ウイルスプログラムが侵入し―
They transmitted a virus program
to the cyborgs, triggering the uprising.
暴動が起こったと考えられます
What we don't know...
しかし同時に―
is how regular non-cyborg humans
were involved in the attack as well.
サイボーグでない
人も襲撃に参加した事実があり
But the investigation is still under way
and we should know more soon.
この原因は まだ調査中です
Right now, evidence suggests
cyborg terrorists were behind this attack.
これでサイバーテロであることは
決定的となった
Whether or not Aeacus was collaborating
with the terrorists remains to be seen.
アイアコス隊員が
テロの協力者かどうかは―
まだ調査中だが
At the same time,
we can't ignore the possibility...
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.の
ウイルスプロテクトが
破られた可能性も捨てきれない
that ES.W.A.T.'s
virus protection programs for cyborgs...
may have been compromised.
状況が確定するまで
So effective immediately, we will suspend
participation of cyborg troops.
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.もサイボーグ隊員の
作戦参加を見合わせる
- What?
- This is bullshit.
（隊員１）
ちょっと待ってください
人は野放しってことですか？
- Non-cyborgs were involved as well.
- You treat us like criminals for this.
（隊員２）
俺たちだけ犯罪者扱いですか！
As long as the enemy's objectives
remain unclear, we have no choice.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
敵の目的が判明しない以上
やむをえない
That is all. Dismissed.
以上だ　解散！
Man, forget this. I'm out of here.
I don't need this crap.
I'm with you.
Yoshitsune.
義経
Yeah?
Would you run some tests on this?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
これ 調べてくれない？
うん 生体チップかな？
何か事件と関係が？
Some sort of biochip?
Where did you get this from?
Off one of the rioters.
Just check it out for me, will you?
分かんないけど
何か気になるの
- No problem. I'll check it out.
- Thanks a lot.
分かった　やってみるよ
ありがとう
Tereus.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
テレウス
Let's have a drink.
飲みに行こう
No, thanks, I'm busy.
俺はいいよ
バックアップはポイントマンに従う
The backup always follows the point man.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ハア… だとさ
You heard the lady.
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
各国の衛星の統合管理と
情報の共有は―
Centralized management
of each country's satellites...
along with the proposed system
of information sharing...
戦後の世界平和を願う人々の
悲願への第一歩と言えます
could be a first step towards fulfilling
the wishes of those who long for peace...
この成果を大きなステップとして
恒久的な平和への…
in our postwar society.
ねえ どこ行く？
ビアホール？　スポーツバー？
So where to?
Feel like a pub or sports bar?
（２人）
スポーツバー
- Sports bar.
いや やっぱりビアホ…
- Pub. That's what I meant to...
アッハハハッ
アッハハハッ　ウフフフ
（ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
いよいよ歴史的な瞬間を迎えました
We go now live to a message
from Prime Minister Athena.
アテナ行政総監による発表です
Momentarily, we will demonstrerte...
（ｱﾃﾅ）
これより32か国482機の
人工衛星の管理を―
what can happen when the satellites
of 32 nations come together...
to form a willing alliance.
オリュンポスに統合する
（ｱﾃﾅ）
ギリシャ神話で
平和と繁栄の象徴と言われる―
According to Greek mythology...
the olive tree
is a symbol of peace and prosperity.
オリーブの木だ
平和を願う思いが
世界を１つにしていくだろう
It is my belief
that mankind's desire for peace...
will soon unite our world.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）カーニバルみたい
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）ハハッ すごいな
- It's like a Carnival.
- Yeah. Looks like fun.
Look out!
ブリアレオス
Briareos!
無人だと？　おりゃ～！
Nobody's driving it.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）情報端末だ
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）ブリアレオス
- The information terminal?
- Briareos!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）ふんっ！
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）ああっ
Stop it. What's gotten into you?
What's wrong with you?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
やめて ブリ！
どうしちゃったんだよ！
何やってんだよ！
Look out!
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
危ない！　うん やめろ
Tereus!
テレウス
What's happening to you?
どうしちゃったんだよ！
ブリアレオス やめろ！
Briareos, stop it.
I said, stop, Briareos!
ねえ ブリアレオス！　ねえ！
ううん… うん！　ねえ！
What are you doing?
Briareos!
Error in the satellite monitoring system!
（隊員１）
衛星監視システムにエラー
Electrical supply system malfunction!
（隊員２）
電源供給システムも不調
We're being hacked into from the outside!
Code yellow!
外部からのハッキングです
コードイエロー
Go to subsystem B, just to be safe.
（隊員３）
念のため
予備のシステムに切り替えろ
Copy that. Switching to B.
（隊員１）
了解　サブシステム作動します
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
現場付近では例の異常電波も
確認されてないし
The unidentified data frequency
wasn't detected in that area.
そのせいじゃないだろうって
So they ruled that out as the cause.
I think they wanna conduct drug tests
and a psych exam on him.
これから薬物検査
精神鑑定が始まるらしいわ
彼はどこに？
So where is he now?
He's here, in the isolation ward.
ここの隔離病棟
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
会ったのか？
Did you see him?
He didn't want me to, so no.
会いたくないって
そうか
I see.
私やります
- I can do that.
- Of course.
（看護師）
すみません
じゃあ お願いしようかしら
I'll go on my rounds and be right back.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
背中
Turn around.
Okay. Thanks.
悪いな
This birthmark.
このアザ
Briareos had the same one.
ブリアレオスと同じ…
どうしちゃったんだよ
ブリアレオス
What's happening to Briareos?
（義経）
デュナンが持ってきた
機械の残骸は―
That biochip you wanted me to check out?
Part of a Connexus.
コネクサスの一部でした
コネクサスを付けた
モルモットです
I put a Connexus on this lab rat.
Watch what happens
when I transmit the same frequency...
こいつにハトロボットの
マイクロチップから―
読み取った信号を発信すると
from one of the robotic doves
to this rat.
It's like he has no control.
意識を乗っ取られる？
コネクサスは生物神経組織に―
When activated, the Connexus emits
a signal that stimulates nerve tissue.
至近距離で作用する
電波を出すようです
つまり こいつを利用すれば
In other words,
it can potentially be used...
人もサイボーグも
同様に操ることができるんです
to manipulate
both humans and cyborgs at will.
That would explain why non-cyborgs
were involved in the attack.
それによって
人も暴動に加わっていたのか？
はい
Exactly.
So that means Aeacus
was innocent, then.
じゃあ アイアコスは
無実だったんだね？
やはり彼も犠牲者の１人だ
Just being used
like the people in the riots were.
This isn't simple cyborg terrorism.
そう考えると
犯人の狙いは
サイボーグのテロなんかじゃなく
もっと大規模な…
This is something much bigger.
国際会議のテロも
テストにすぎないってこと？
Then the terrorist attack on Tartaros
was just some kind of test.
I don't know how, but we gotta
get these things off the street.
すぐにコネクサスを
使用禁止にしてください
Is it true?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
本当に俺がデュナンを襲ったのか？
Did I really attack Deunan?
どうなっちまったんだ 俺は！
What's happening to me?! What?!
They don't know,
and that's why She's worried.
デュナンもひどく心配してたわ
会いたいって
She wants to see you.
No.
Not now.
今はダメだ
Maybe there's something I can do.
私にできることある？
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
リヒャルト･ケスナー
Richard Kestner.
2135年よりオリュンポス
科学アカデミーに所属
He's been with the Olympus
Science Academy since 2135...
but he worked for Poseidon before that.
その前はポセイドンに
いたみたいね
Poseidon?
ポセイドン？
もっと情報が欲しい
Keep going. What else does it say?
Let me try to access
Olympus' host computer.
ガイアのホストコンピューターに
アクセスしてみるわ
Chief Technician of New Technology
Elizabeth Xander.
“技術主任エリザベス･ザンダー”
Halcon Laboratory.
“ハルコン ラボラトリー”
- Halcon?
- I'll look it up.
ハルコン？
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
調べてみる
Everything has been erased.
消されてる？
Is Kestner behind this?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ケスナーの仕業か？
Kestner never would have been able
to remove that amount of data...
世界中のネットワークから
全てのデータを消すなんて
彼一人でできることじゃないわ
もっと大きな力が動いてる
from a global network on his own.
Someone else must be behind this.
ポセイドンか…
It must be Poseidon.
Hitomi, cover your ears.
ヒトミ 耳をふさげ！
Briareos, no! Stop it.
ダメよ！　ブリアレオス
- I need to pay the good doctor a visit!
- Please, don't do this! You could get...
ヤツに会って確かめたいんだ
（ﾋﾄﾐ）
やめて！
そんなことしたら あなたが…
- Over here!
- Hey!
（看護師１）
こっちだ
（看護師２）
あなた 何してるんですか！
まだ傷口がふさがってないのに
Where do you think you're going?
We have to evacuate the hospital.
- You get out, I have to find someone. Go.
- You can't. We have to leave.
ヤツを…
ブリアレオスを追わないと
（看護師２）
部屋に戻りなさい
Aren't you listening to me?
Leave me alone.
ヤツの暴走を止めなければ！
Hang on.
突っ切るわよ！
Attention, citizens: The Connexus
is now considered to be a harmful product.
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
市民の皆さんにお知らせします
コネクサスは有害商品の
指定を受けました
If you are a Connexus user...
市民の皆さんにお知らせします
- What are they talking about?
- I can't live without this thing.
（男性１）
どういうこと？
（男性２）
そんなこと言われてもな～
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
お持ちの方は最寄りの行政機関に
ご提出ください
Repeat, the Connexus is considered
to be a harmful product.
We'll be lucky if even 10 percent
of the population turn them in.
（ｱﾃﾅ）
回収できるものは
恐らく１割とあるまい
I want enforcement measures
taken as early as tomorrow.
明日にも強制措置を執るように
- Of course.
- Nike.
はい
（隊員）ニケ参長
（ニケ）なんだ？
- What is it?
- Briareos has escaped from the hospital.
（隊員）
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.のサイボーグが
ヒトミ政務次官を人質に―
He's taken Vice Minister Hitomi hostage.
逃走しました
You're all aware of Briareos' capabilities.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
ブリアレオスの力は
みんなよく知っているな
Don't you ever let your guard down.
くれぐれも気を抜くな！
All right, move out.
よし いけ！
Deunan Knute.
デュナン･ナッツ
I want you to withdraw
from this assignment.
お前はこの任務から外れろ
- What are you talking about?
- That's a direct order. You understand me?
なぜですか？
これは命令だ　分かるな？
お前はここで待機 いいな！
Remain here on standby. Got it?
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
その車両
直ちに路肩に寄って停止しなさい
Pull your vehicle
to the side of the road immediately.
Surrender or we will take hostile action.
ムダな逃走は諦めろ
- What do we do?
- Do what they want.
どうする？
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
これ以上は無理か
Irepeat, stop your vehicle immediately.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
繰り返す　直ちに停止しなさい
巻き込んで悪かったな
Thanks for the lift.
- Do you want a gun?
- Don't need one.
銃は？
必要ない
We've taken the hostage
into protective custody.
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
人質は無事保護しました
The fugitive's whereabouts
are still unknown.
ブリアレオスの行方は
依然不明です
So where is he? Where did he go?
ブリアレオスはどこですか？
分かるわけないわ
Why are you asking me?
How would I know?
なぜ私に？
If you don't answer me,
I will simply ask myself.
あなたが答えてくれないなら
俺自身に聞いてみます
Then I'll know where to go.
ヤツなら どう動くか
It looks like the fugitive
took Harbor Way Number 4...
（隊員）
ブリアレオスは
ハーバーハイウェー４号を―
シグナスストリート付近で
降りた模様
and exited Somewhere near Cygnus.
We're currently inspecting all vehicles
within a 1 -kilometer radius of the area.
エリアを半径１kmに絞って検問中
各隊員は連携して捜査に当たれ
You should do some decorating.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
殺風景な部屋だな
I can tell you live alone.
侘びしい１人暮らしか？
Oh, no.
違うな　私は１人ではない
I am never exactly alone.
What have you done to my body?
俺の体に何をした？
外部からの電波では―
It's impossible to control your body
using data frequencies from the outside.
君の体をコントロールすることは
不可能だ
君の事故は好都合だったよ
Fortunately, your little incident
gave me the perfect opportunity...
to add a rather special feature to
that Hecatonchire body of yours.
やっかいなヘカトンケイル級には
特別サービスをした
Nanomachines.
ナノマシンだ
ナノマシンだと？
You did what?
They're ravenous feeders,
and now they feed off of you.
そいつの餌は君自身だ
It's a fascinating program, really...
君のアドレナリン分泌量が
ある一定の数値を超えると
activated the instant
that your adrenaline levels...
発動するようにプログラムしてある
rise just beyond a certain point.
君が起こしたハッキング事件も
全て予定どおりだ
You do realize that the hacking incident
you caused was all part of the plan.
人工衛星管制センターの
メインルームへの侵入は―
You see, I found
it would be very difficult...
to infiltrate the main control room
of the satellite command center.
難しかったのでね
So I performed a little trick
on their backup module.
バックアップシステムに細工をした
All that was needed then
was to crash the main system.
あとはメインシステムを
ダウンさせるだけだった
And you did that wonderfully.
君はよくやってくれた
Why are you doing this?
一体 何が目的なんだ？
Do you know why this world
can never exist without bloodshed?
世界でなぜ殺し合いが絶えないか
分かるかね？
Individual differences, of course.
個体差だよ
違う体 違う心
それが全ての争いの本質だ
Different hearts, different minds.
That is the essence of all conflict.
But if our world was converted
to a single, united consciousness...
だから我々は
１つの意識体となる
１つの意識？
テロを仕掛けたのもお前か？
You're the one.
You're the one behind the attacks.
No. I have comrades all over the world.
同志は世界中にいる
俺の体を元に戻せ！
Fix what you've done to me!
It's too late for that.
もう手遅れだ
時間だ
And now, it's time.
System error.
We've lost control of the satellites.
（隊員１）
システムエラー
衛星のコントロールができません
All links to the satellites are cut off.
全てのサテライトの
認可が失われています
What the hell is going on?
（隊員２）
一体どうなってる？
（隊員１）
バックアップシステムに異常が
- Backup system's out too.
- Try it again.
なんだと！
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
何を始める気だ？
What are you trying to do?
Assimilation and natural selection.
勇猛と淘汰(とうた)
Those that cannot be integrated
will be eliminated.
１つになれないものは
消えていく
Thanks to the Connexus
and the global satellite network...
コネクサスと衛星ネットによって
人々は意識レベルで１つになり
mankind will be united
once and for all.
もう誤解も差別もない
世界が生まれる
Imagine a world without
misunderstanding or discrimination.
そして争いも戦いもなくなる
The elimination of all human conflict
and the banishment of war.
My vision and Halcon's ideals
will finally become our reality and truth.
ハルコンの理想が
ついに現実になるのだよ！
- Halcon.
- The global security network is down.
ハルコン？
（隊員）
グローバル･セキュリティー･ネット
システムダウン
We've lost control of the satellites. Repeat,
we've lost control of the satellites.
全ての衛星が
コントロール不能
グローバル･セキュリティー･ネット
システムダウン！
They waited for the satellites to unite
before hijacking them.
衛星を統合させておいて
奪い取る
国際会議のテロは
そこまで計算した上で…
Even the attack on the peace summit
must have been thoroughly designed.
Prime minister, if they use...
もし全ての衛星から
コネクサスへの信号が
発信されたとしたら
If they transmit that signal to Connexus
via satellites...
- Nike, issue an alert to the alliance nations.
- At once.
各国に緊急警戒態勢を発令！
（ニケ）
はい
（ｹｽﾅｰ）
もうすぐ もうすぐ君にも分かる
Don't worry.
My friend,
in but a moment you will understand.
肉体など ただの器にすぎん
Mechanical or not,
our bodies are just vessels.
我々は魂を解放するのだ
We must set ourselves free.
Kestner. Don't do it!
待て！　やめろ！
- We've got him! He's here!
- Stay where you are. Don't move!
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ１）
ここだ！　いたぞ！
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ２）
動くな！
Freeze! Put your hands up! Now!
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ１）
ブリアレオスだな？
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ３）
逃走中のＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.隊員
ブリアレオスを発見
We've found the fugitive cyborg.
There's a man down. Send an ambulance.
１人撃たれて倒れています
救急車を！
動くな
- Hold it.
- Freeze!
待て！
飛び降りたのか？
Shit, he jumped.
He went down.
落ちたぞ
Suspect jumped out of the window.
Find him!
下だ 追え！
犯人は窓より飛び降りた
追跡を続ける
We will continue pursuit.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
ブリアレオスはまだ逃走中だ
至急発見し確保せよ
Briareos is still on the run.
He's considered armed and dangerous.
If he resists...
ヤツは危険な状態だ
抵抗する場合は―
you're authorized to use lethal force.
射殺を許可する
（ﾗﾝｽ）
繰り返す　ブリアレオスは
Lrepeat, Briareos is still on the run.
シグナスストリートを
南下中と思われる
世界が終わっても
お前を守ってみせる
I'll always protect you,
even if the world comes to an end.
義経
- I need your help.
- You're gonna go after him, aren't you?
止めてもムダそうだな
When you find him, use these.
これをブリアレオスに
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
これは？
What are they?
Parasite antitoxins.
（義経）
パラサイトカウンター
大戦中サイボーグの
サイバーテロ対策に開発された
They were developed during the war as
a countermeasure against cyber-terrorism.
一種のショック療法で
意識を取り戻させる
It's like shock treatment for cyborgs.
It should help him regain consciousness.
ブリアレオスが
またヤバくなったら
If he starts to lose it,
shoot this into his nervous system...
これを首筋から神経系に
直接打ち込むんだ
from the back of his neck,
if you can get it there.
So this can save him?
これで助かるの？
It's just an emergency measure,
but it's better than nothing.
急場しのぎだが
ないよりはマシだ
Thanks for doing this.
義経 ありがとう
I owe you one.
Good luck.
えいっ
Briareos.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
ブリアレオス
やっぱり ここに来たな
I knew you'd come here.
You know every move I'm
gonna make, don't you?
俺の考えは手に取るように
読めるってわけか
I'm taking you in, Briareos.
おとなしく投降しろ
Don't come any closer.
それ以上 近づくな
限界だ…
I can't control myself.
Briareos!
ブリアレオス
お前は誰だ？
Who are you?
Why is there another one of me?
なぜ…
なぜ俺がもう１人いるんだ！
Why do you have what I've lost?
なぜ お前は
俺が失ったものを持ってる
なぜだ！
全ては１つ…
Everything will unite...
Get out of my head!
俺を呼ぶな～！
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Deunan.
デュナン
Briareos!
ブリアレオス！
テレウス ブリを押さえて
Tereus, hold him down.
ブリアレオス ああっ
Briareos.
It's no use, Deunan.
ムダだ デュナン
ブリアレオスはもう…
We have to...
Shut up and hold him.
冗談じゃないわ
絶対に…
I'm not giving up on you.
あなたを…
Open your eyes!
取り戻す！
Briareos.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス
Briareos.
ブリアレオス　ブリアレオス
Deunan?
デュナン
It's me, I'm here.
分かるんだね ブリ
I'm here.
I'm always here.
よかった
I have to take him in, Deunan.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
悪いが ブリアレオスの身柄は
俺が確保する
Tereus...
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
テレウス
It's too late.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
もう遅い
何が始まるの？
What is going on?
I'm registering riot Codes everywhere.
（隊員１）
オリュンポス全域で暴動が発生
規模は現在確認中
Multiple signals.
Riots are breaking out across Olympus.
（隊員２）
各国との通信網が遮断されています
状況を把握できません
We've lost communication
with the other countries.
（隊員３）
強力な異常電波を確認
発信源は各国の人工衛星からです
Unidentified data frequencies confirmed.
It's being broadcast from the satellites.
これは世界中で起きているのか？
Everywhere?
This is happening all over the world.
もはや… これは戦争です
It's war. This is how the war begins.
ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.はポリスと連携して
暴徒の鎮圧に当たれ
ES.W.A.T. will work in conjunction
with the police to suppress the riots.
彼らはテロリストではなく
操られただけの市民だ
But remember, they're not terrorists,
just ordinary civilians being manipulated.
極力 殺傷は避けろ
No excessive force unless you have to.
But don't forget
these riots must be stopped.
ただし 最悪の場合は…
暴動鎮圧を最優先する
分かるな！
By any means necessary.
来るな 来るなよ
Stop walking. Just stop.
Son of a bitch! How's this happening?
おい なぜ こんなことに！
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
コネクサスで市民を操り
全世界を支配する
Everyone Who's hooked into Connexus
is being controlled...
is that what you're telling me?
それが敵の目的なのか？
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
マズいぞ　こっちだ！
What do we do?
- This way!
- This is getting bad.
ここもダメか
これじゃ きりがない
- I've got signals everywhere.
- We have to destroy the source.
大本を絶たないと
“ハルコン”
ケスナーはそう言った
"Halcon," that's what Kestner called it.
ポセイドンだ
ヤツらは何かを隠している
Poseidon is behind all this...
and they're hiding something.
Poseidon's ship and their emissary
have already left, but they can't be far.
ポセイドンの特使を乗せた船が
近海にいるはずだ
Let's go, we can do it.
行こう ブリアレオス！
Tereus, come in.
（ﾗﾝｽ）
テレウス 応答せよ
各地で暴動が発生している
Have you located Briareos?
ブリアレオスは確保したか？
状況を報告しろ
Lrepeat, have you located Briareos?
Report your status.
This is Tereus.
こちらテレウス
Briareos is...
ブリアレオスは…
He's dead, sir.
射殺　繰り返す
ブリアレオスは射殺
I repeat, Briareos is dead.
応援は不要
No need to send backup.
はあ～ あんたらのおかげで
初めてウソをついた
And thanks to you two,
I just told my first lie.
All right, let's go. I mean, I...
俺も行く
俺はデュナンのパートナーだからな
I can't go back to the station now, can I?
I guess not.
テレウス
Move it. They don't fly themselves.
デュナン 持ってきたぞ！
（隊員）
暴徒は数十万人規模と思われます
Mob numbers
are in the hundreds of thousands.
皆 各エリアから―
My readings say
they're heading towards Tartaros.
このタルタロスに
向かってきている模様
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）
持ちこたえろ！
極力 惨状は避けるんだ
Hold your positions!
Avoid deadly force if at all possible!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
あれだ
That's it.
We're in a hurry.
No time for introductions.
急いでるんだ
挨拶は省くぞ
I know why you're here.
（吉野）
分かっています
We need to know two things:
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
知りたいのは２つだけだ
What is Halcon
and where can we find it?
ハルコンとはなんだ？
そして どこにある？
Halcon is no more.
ハルコンは もともとポセイドンの
一研究部門でした
But once it was Poseidon's
leading research and development lab.
エリザベス･ザンダー教授を中心に
Professor Elizabeth Xander
was the head of research.
彼らは 大戦の被害で
障害を抱えた人々の―
They designed and developed
rehabilitation de vices. ..
For those who had sustained
severe head trauma in the war.
更生用デバイスとプログラムを
開発していました
彼らは人工知能と
サイボーグ技術によって
Using artificial intelligence
and cyborg technologies...
they saved hundreds of the wounded.
多くの戦争被害者を救った
まるで神のように
Almost like a god...
その自信が彼らの心に
ゆがんだ平和思想を生んだのです
Their pride led them to develop
a distorted sense of reality.
Did Halcon Laboratories
invent the Connexus?
コネクサスも
ハルコンの発明なんだね？
恐らく
Most likely.
They were obsessed with mind control.
彼らのやり方は
ただのマインドコントロールです
We shut them down immediately.
Everyone was fired.
本社は即刻ハルコンを閉鎖
スタッフを解雇しました
Soon thereafter...
その直後―
Elizabeth Xander died in an accident.
ザンダー教授は事故死を遂げました
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
お前らがやったんだろ！
That doesn't exonerate you.
You silenced them to
protect the conglomerate.
企業さえ守りゃそれでい
その傲慢な考えが このザマだ
And now this is the end result.
Tell me where Halcon is.
どこにあるんだ ハルコンは？
This is Halcon's zero-gravity plant.
（吉野）
これがハルコンの
海上無重力プラントです
かなり前に売却されて
We sold it ages ago.
It's been abandoned for years...
現在は大規模な
無人の工場になっていたはずですが
そう遠くない　ハルコンに行く
It's not far from here.
I'm going in.
I'm going to destroy
Halcon before it destroys me.
そいつに取り込まれる前に
この手でたたきつぶす！
We have to reclaim control.
取り戻さなくちゃ
私たちの世界を！
We can supply you with the latest
Weapons and a small task force.
（吉野）
あなたたちには最新鋭の
装備と兵力をご提供いたします
It's the least that we can do.
これが我が社の誠意です
This is Arges.
He will take care of the rest.
あとは このアルゲスが
We'll meet up at the location.
Let's go.
我々も現地へ向かう
すぐに出発だ
A human, a bioroid and a cyborg.
（吉野）
人とバイオロイドとサイボーグ
あの３人がオリュンポスの希望か
The fate of Olympus
rests in their hands.
How does it look?
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
どうだ？　ポセイドンの最新型は？
It's a prototype, but I should be fine.
プロトタイプだけど
使いこなしてみせるわ
If we stop the Halcon signal,
are you going to be okay?
ハルコンからの信号を止められれば
ブリの体も治るの？
そう祈っててくれ
Let's hope so.
The target should be in sight soon.
All Landmates, prepare for takeoff.
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
まもなく目標が視界に入る
全ランドメイト発進準備
So this is Halcon.
これがハルコン
思った以上にデカいな
It's a hell of a lot
bigger than I imagined.
Halcon's main computer should
be located in the central core.
この中心部に
ハルコンの中枢があるはずだ
Our unit will escort the
three Olympus Landmates.
我々の部隊はオリュンポスの
３機をエスコートして―
ハルコンの中枢部まで向かう
There's no way to know what's
inside, but we must stop it. Understood?
何が待ってるか分からんが
なんとしてもハルコンの
テロを止める　いいな！
幸い 下の海上都市は
すでに無人となっている
Luckily, there should be nobody inside.
Use your weapons freely!
思いきり暴れて問題ない！
It's moving.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
動きだした
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
気をつけろ！
Watch out!
Move to the right!
右の溝に飛び込め
What the hell?
うわっ なんだ！
Incoming!
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
また来る！
Central core coming up
after we get through this Corridor.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
この回廊を抜ければ
中心部に出るはずだ
Is this it?
ここは？
That must be the core.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
あれがハルコンの中枢か
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
見ろ！
さっきのドローンの大群だ！
It's those drones again.
Get ready!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
来るぞ！
起動しながら応戦するんだ！
止まるとやられるぞ
Don't stop moving!
Don't Stand still!
Shit!
Briareos?
ブリアレオス
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
なにっ！
No!
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス！　うっ…
Briareos!
Get away!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
やめろ～！
ブリアレオス
Briareos!
It's me!
気付いて！
ううう… デュナン…
Deunan.
You all right?
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
大丈夫か？　２人とも
ハァ ハァ…
大丈夫だ すまない
I'm all right. Thanks.
Another wave coming in.
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
第２波が来るぞ！
Keep it tight, people.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
みんな密集体系をとれ
残った兵力で一気に中枢を目指す
Concentrate remaining forces
on reaching the target.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
テレウス
Tereus, I have one dose left...
薬はあと１本だけだ
これ以上すると
俺の神経がもたない
but I know my body.
My nerves can't handle another dose.
今度おかしくなったら終わりだ
その時は かまわず俺を撃て！
If I lose it again...
I want you to take me out.
You understand?
Why do you ask me?
なぜ俺に？
I need you to.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
頼む
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
ブリアレオス
Briareos...
Incoming!
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
来るぞ！
Maintain formation.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
フォーメーションを崩すな
このまま突っ切るんだ！
Cut straight through them.
What the hell have we got now?
更に新手かよ
何！　うわ～！
しまった　早い
Shit! He's quick!
この弾じゃ効かない
The bullets aren't damaging him!
- Deunan, are you all right?
- Yeah!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
デュナン 大丈夫か？
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）うん
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）もう一体は？
There's another one.
Over there.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
あそこか！
ブリ テレウス 私たちならやれる！
Come on, guys.
- Let's get him.
- We'll distract the drones.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
俺たちがドローンを引きつける
デュナンはあいつを！
- Take him out.
- No problem.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
分かった
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
いけデュナン！　ここは任せろ！
Move it, Deunan.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
うまく引きつけろよ
- Watch your back.
- You watch yours.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
あんたこそ
Out of bullets.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
弾切れか
え～い！
フンッ　うお～！
どこ？
Where is he?
いや～！
Is that all you've got?
いけ～！
Take this!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
おりゃ～！
ええ～い！
すごいヤツらです　うん？
These guys are insane.
中枢のゲートが閉じていく
The central gate! It's closing!
俺はゲートを確保
テレウス お前はデュナンを！
I got it.
Tereus, take care of Deunan.
One step ahead of you.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
分かってる
Move it.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
急げ！
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）デュナン
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）テレウス
- Deunan.
- Tereus.
Gotcha.
（ﾃﾚｳｽ）
いくぞ
Tereus, hurry.
テレウス 急げ！
強制除装と同時に飛び込むぞ！
- We're gonna eject, then we jump through.
- Do it.
了解
来るな！　来るな！　来るな！
Stay back! I said stay back!
What cannot become one
will be eliminated.
（男）
１つになれない者は消えていく
（ﾎﾟﾘｽ）やめろ！
（銃声）
Stop it!
大丈夫か？
Daddy? Daddy, get UP-
パパ　パパ 起きて！
パパ！　パパ！
Daddy! Daddy!
（隊員１）
ポリスレーダー応答せよ
Section E Commander, come in.
（隊員２）
モニターカメラが破壊されています
The security cameras
have been destroyed.
（隊員３）
Ｓ地区とも連絡が取れません
We can't seem to contact
Section S, either.
（隊員４）
オリュンポス全域
モニタリング不能
All monitoring systems
in Olympus have been lost.
こちらランス　ＥＳ.Ｗ.Ａ.Ｔ.部隊
各自状況を知らせろ
This is your Captain.
All ES.W.A.T. troops, report your status.
応答せよ！　応答せよ！
Come in. Come in.
What is happening to Olympus?
（ｱﾃﾅ）
一体どうなっている？
オリュンポスは
It's Xander.
あれがザンダー？
Kestner brought her back to life.
ケスナーたちが生き返らせたんだ
Briareos!
ブリアレオス
デュナン
（撃鉄を起こす音）
Deunan.
（ｻﾞﾝﾀﾞｰ）
撃つがいい
Go ahead and shoot.
私を殺せば―
Just be aware that if you kill me...
同時にハルコンと
同化した人間たちも失うことになる
all of the ones who have merged
with Halcon will be lost forever.
That, of course, will include
this Hecatonchire as well.
もちろん その
ヘカトンケイレスもな
What are we gonna do?
どうすれば
ハルコンを止められるの？
How are we gonna stop this thing?
That would be impossible.
諦めろ
Surrender yourselves now
and become one with Halcon.
そして お前たちも
ハルコンと１つになれ
デュナン うっ…
Deunan.
ブリアレオス 答えて
ブリアレオス！
Briareos. Answer me!
Briareos!
こんな… ここで…
Is this it?
Briareos?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
ブリアレオス
Part of Xander is still human.
You must find her consciousness.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
ザンダーにも どこかにまだ
人の心が残っているはずだ
デュナン
Deunan!
（ｻﾞﾝﾀﾞｰ）
私を… 助けて…
Somebody... Help me...
Forcing everybody's
consciousness together...
心ってもんはね うっ！
人から１つにしてもらうもんじゃ
ないのよ！
doesn't create anything whole!
Deunan...
デュナン うっ…
これを… ザンダーに…
use this.
Do it, Deunan!
いけ デュナン！
それほど死にたいか？
I see that you wish to die.
テレウス！
Tereus!
Xander, we were both artificially created.
ザンダー 俺もお前も作り物の人だ
だけど…
うっ…
心は誰のものでもない
But our hearts...
Our souls are not artificial.
自分だけのものだ
聞こえるか？
Can you hear me, Xander?
Wake up!
本当のお前を取り戻すんだ！
ザンダー！
デュナン
Deunan.
I've reset Halcon's signals.
ハルコンの全ての信号を
リセットしました
Xander, you're conscious!
ザンダー
本物のザンダーなのね？
今のうちに私を破壊して
Deunan, destroy me while you still can.
It's the only way
to stop the Halcon system.
ハルコンシステムを
完全に止めるのです
Destroy me before...
私がまた
機械に支配される前に
Kestner's machine
takes control of me...
again.
早く！
撃つんだ デュナン！
Deunan, shoot her!
Xander...
ザンダー
Now I can die as a human.
これで人として死ねる
ありがとう
Thank you.
I'm so...
ごめんな… さ い
so sorry.
This is Sector J-4.
（隊員）
こちらＪ４地区
タルタロスに向かっていた暴徒が
次々に倒れています
The rioters have all started collapsing
en masse.
暴徒の動きが止まりました
They've just stopped moving.
The unidentified data frequency
has stopped transmission.
（隊員１）
異常電波 消滅しました
（隊員２）
衛星ネットのコントロールも回復
The satellites are back online.
The rioters appear to be collapsing.
（隊員３）
各地で暴徒と化していた市民が―
気を失って倒れているようです
（ﾗﾝｽ）どういうことだ？
What the hell's going on?
Is it over?
助かったのか？
Briareos! Are you all right?
大丈夫？　ブリアレオス
I'm okay, Deunan.
ああ 大丈夫だ！　デュナン
You're sure, right?
今度こそ本当に治ったんだね
Kestner's plan failed. It's over.
どうやら
１つになり損ねたらしいな
Tereus!
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
テレウス
This is gonna hurt.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
我慢しろよ
Let's hurry!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
急ごう！
Where's Arges?
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
アルゲスたちは？
It's falling apart!
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
崩れるぞ
テレウス！
Tereus!
もういい 俺を置いていけ
Just leave me here.
（ﾌﾞﾘｱﾚｵｽ）
バカ言うな！　仲間だろ！
Shut up and get up!
We aren't leaving you behind!
I'm just a bioroid.
俺はバイオロイドだ
いくらでも作れる
- They can make another one.
- That's not true!
違う！
テレウスに代わりなんか
いるわけない！
We're not gonna leave you, Tereus.
あんたは１人だけなんだよ
そうだろ？
No one can replace you.
Right?
Arges!
アルゲス
Let's go! Hurry!
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
急いでくれ！　時間がない！
Let's go, Tereus!
行くよ テレウス！
Come on!
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
もう もたねえぞ！
Jump for it!
Let's get out of here!
（ｱﾙｹﾞｽ）
脱出するぞ
また 全てやり直しです
We're back to the drawing board.
That's true.
しかし 我々は皆
こうして生きている
But all that matters is
that we have survived.
We will forge ahead.
We can never give up.
諦めず 前を見て進むだけだ
希望はまだある
Hope is not lost.
Thank you...
ありがとう デュナン
Deunan.
ウフッ
世界が終わっても
お前を守ってみせる
I'll always protect you,
even if the world comes to an end.
ハハッ　それは俺のセリフだろ
Now, where have I heard that before?
You remembered.
（ﾃﾞｭﾅﾝ）
覚えててくれたのね
How could I forget?
You gonna fight for her?
いいのか？
No, I'll find someone.
いいんです　俺も探します
守りたい誰かをね
Someone whom I wish to protect.
よし　お客さんを
オリュンポスまでお送りするぞ
Time to get you guys back to Olympus.
A Team Nanban (594mgnav) Release